

ASSISTANT PROFESSOR

2-24-16, Naka-cho, Koganei, Tokyo, 184-8588, JAPAN

□ (+81) 42-388-7458 | ■ nkita@go.tuat.ac.jp | ♣ naokita.xyz

Summary _

I am an assistant professor at Tokyo University of Agriculture and Technology. I received my Ph.D. at Japan Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (JAIST). I received my B.S. degree in science from Kanazawa University in 2009, and my M.S. in knowledge science from JAIST in 2011. My current research interests include computational design/fabrication and human visual perception, especially in layout/arrangement for discrete elements.

Education

JAIST (Japan Advanced Institute of Science and Technology)

Japan

Ph.D. in Knowledge Science Apr. 2016 - Mar. 2019

· Advisor: Kazunori Miyata

JAIST (Japan Advanced Institute of Science and Technology)

Japa

M.S. IN KNOWLEDGE SCIENCE

Apr. 2009 - Mar. 2011

- Thesis: Interactive Procedural Modeling of Pebble Mosaics
- Advisor: Kazunori Miyata

Kanazawa University

Japan

B.S. IN SCIENCE Apr. 2005 - Mar. 2009

· Advisor: Toyoko Arai

Experience _____

Visual Computing Laboratory, Tokyo University of Agriculture and Technology

Japan

Apr. 2019 - PRESENT

READi Design Lab, L'École de design Nantes Atlantique

France

VISITING RESEARCHER Feb. 2017 - Nov. 2017

• Joined IDEA (Immersive Data Exploration & Analysis) project and developed immersive VR applications.

JAIST-DNIC (Dependable Network Innovation Center)

Japar

PROJECT RESEARCHER Aug. 2013 - Mar. 2016

Developed a skill map for CYDER (CYber Defense Exercise with Recurrence) project hosted by Ministry of Internal Affairs and Communications.

Kanazawa Medical University

Japan

COLLABORATIVE RESEARCHER Apr. 2011 - Mar. 2016

• Developed a NRBCs (Nucleated Red Blood Cell) autodetect system for non-invasive fetal DNA diagnosis from maternal blood.

Allied Telesis Research Institute, Ltd.

Japan

SOFTWARE ENGINEER Feb. 2015 - Oct. 2015

- Developed a in-house web service in Scala/Play Framework.
- Developed an e-learning system in Moodle and a cyber security lecture course on it.

JAIST (Japan Advanced Institute of Science and Technology)

Japan

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Apr. 2012 - Mar. 2013

IPA MITOH Program

Japan

PROJECT LEADER Feb. 2012 - Aug. 2012

• Funded for half a year as a project leader of an exploratory IT Human Resources Project (THE MITOH Program), and developed a discrete element texture generation application.

Publications

INTERNATIONAL JOURNALS

- N. Kita and K. Miyata, "Magic sheets: Visual cryptography with common shares", Computational Visual Media, Vol.4, No.2, pp.185–195, 2018.
- N. Kita and K. Miyata, "Aesthetic Rating and Color Suggestion for Color Palettes", Computer Graphics Forum, Vol.35, No.7, pp.127–136, 2016.
- N. Kita and K. Miyata, "Multi-class anisotropic blue noise sampling for discrete element pattern generation", The Visual Computer, Vol.32, No.6, pp.1035–1044, 2016.

INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCES (ORAL PRESENTATION)

- N. Kita and K. Miyata, "Magic Sheet: Visual Cryptography with Common shares", CVM 2018, Shanghai, China (April 2018).
- N. Kita and K. Miyata, "Aesthetic Rating and Color Suggestion for Color Palettes", Pacific Graphics (PG 2016), Okinawa, Japan (October 2016).
- N. Kita and K. Miyata, "Multi-class anisotropic blue noise sampling for discrete element pattern generation", Computer Graphics International (CGI 2016), Heraklion, Crete, Greece (June 2016).
- N. Kita and K. Miyata, "Interactive Procedural Modeling of Pebble Mosaics", ACM SIGGRAPH Asia 2011 Sketches, ACM SA'11, Article 35, pp.35:1–35:2, Hong Kong, China (December 2011).

K. Ishibashi, T. Da Luz, R. Eynard, N. Kita, N, Jiang, H. Segi, K. Terada, K. Fujita and K. Miyata, "Spider Hero", Laval Virtual Revolution 2010, An.3, Laval, France (April 2010).

K. Ishibashi, T. Da Luz, R. Eynard, N. Kita, N, Jiang, H. Segi, K. Terada, K. Fujita and K. Miyata, "Spider Hero: A VR application using pulling force feedback system", VRCAI 2010, Session 7, Tokyo, Japan (December 2009).

INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCES (POSTER)

- N. Kita and K. Miyata, "Cube Art", ACM SIGGRAPH Asia 2016 Posters, ACM SA'16, Article 30, pp.30:1-30:1, Macau (December 2016).
- N. Kita and K. Miyata, "A rule-based method for generating bookshelf models", ACM SIGGRAPH Asia 2010 Posters, ACM SA'10, Article 36, pp.36:1-36:2, Seoul, Korea (December 2010).

Honors & Awards _____

2019	Outstanding Performance Award in the doctoral program, JAIST
Jul 2018 - Mar 2019	JAIST Research Grant (Fundamental Research) 2018, Japan Advanced Institute of Science and
	Technology
2018	Excellent Poster Award, JAIST World Conference 2018
Apr 2017 - Mar 2019	JSPS Young Research Fellowship (DC2), Japan Society for the Promotion of Science
Feb 2017 - Nov 2017	JAIST Grant for Off-Campus Research, Japan Advanced Institute of Science and Technology
Apr 2016 - Mar 2017	JAIST Doctral Research Fellowship (DRF), Japan Advanced Institute of Science and Technology
2016	Outstanding Poster Award, JAIST HLD International Symposium 2016
Feb 2012 - Aug 2012	The Exploratory IT Human Resources Project (THE MITOH Program), Information Technology
	Promotion Agency Japan (IPA)
2011	Outstanding Performance Award in the master program, JAIST
2011	Best Paper Award, 10th NICOGRAPH Spring
2010	Campus Genius Award SILVER (Interactive), 15th Campus Genius Award

Skills _____

Programming Python, Ruby, C++, C#, Java, JavaScript **Languages** Japanese (Native), English (Intermediate)